http://www.optimummusic.com/privacy

£0.00
Item (0)
Shine
Could This Be?
Could This Be?
Feelings
Have You Ever Loved Somebody?
How Can I?
How Many Times?
The Love In Me And You
What Are You Gonna Do ?
Happy Birthday Suubi
Have I Done Enough To Be To Be Trusted?
Men Productions Ltd
Men Productions Ltd is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. This privacy policy explains how we use the information we collect about you, how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy.
1. The information we collect and how we use it
When you purchase an individual track or album we need to know your name and email address. In addition, our payments processing company PAYPAL will need to know your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number and expiry date. Please note that our site uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology at the ordering stage to protect you when entering your credit card details. This means that any data you enter into the credit card purchase form at the end of the buying process is encrypted to prevent anyone accessing your details. When entering credit card details on this site (or any web site!), always look for the padlock which appears at the bottom right of your web browser.
We gather this information to allow us to process any orders or enquiries you make. The relevant information is then used by us, our agents and sub-contractors to communicate with you on any matter relating to your order and the provision of the service in general.All your personal and credit card details are used by PAYPAL to process your payment.
We may also use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us develop the website and our services and may provide such aggregate information to third parties. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify any individual.
From time to time we may provide your information to our customer service agencies for research and analysis purposes so that we can monitor and improve the services we provide. We or our agents and sub-contractors may contact you to ask you for your feedback and comments on our services.
We may also wish to provide you with information about special features of our website or any other service or products (including those of third parties) we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please send a blank e-mail message to remove@optimummusic.com
2. Our use of cookies and other information gathering technologies.
Cookies are used. Cookies are small text files for storing small pieces of data on a web client (i.e. the web browser on a computer). A web server may store cookies in a user’s browser or request the browser to transmit certain data to the web server.
This information does not in any way reveal any personal data about visitors.
3 How we protect your information
All information i.e. your name and email address, relating to an order is stored on a secure server. We do not sell your data onto anyone else.
We also keep your information confidential. The internal procedures of Men Productions Ltd cover the storage, access and disclosure of your information.
4 Sale of business
If this business is sold or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the business.
5 Updating your details
If any of the information that you have provided to Men Productions Ltd changes, for example if you change your e-mail address, name or if you wish to cancel your registration, please let us know the correct details by sending an e-mail to enquiries@optimummusic.com or by post to Men Productions Ltd, 109 Cedar Road, Sturry, Canterbury, Kent, CT2 0JQ
6 Your consent
By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Continued use of the service will signify that you agree to any such changes.
Owing to the global nature of the Internet infrastructure, the information you provide may be transferred in transit to countries outside the European Economic Area that do not have similar protections in place regarding your data and its use as set out in this policy. However, we have taken the steps outlined above to try to improve the security of your information. By submitting your information you consent to these transfers.
7 How to contact Men Productions Ltd
We welcome your views about our website and our privacy policy. If you would like to contact us with any queries or comments, our contact details are on our contact us page.
Useful Information
Biographies
Videos
FAQs
Music applied to real life
Shine
Always
Im Happy
Could This Be?
Could This Be?
How Can I?
How Many Times?
I accept the terms of the privacy policy (Privacy Policy)
If you would like to receive updates please enter your name and email address below
I accept the terms of the privacy policy (Privacy Policy)
Social Media
Tel:
Email:
Notice:
Optimum Music has updated its website in compliance with the
EU Cookie Legislation.
Please review our policy to find out about which cookies we use and what information we collect on our website.
By continuing to use this site, you are agreeing to our policy.
OK
